Sakura Nishiya Front-end Developer

Vancouver, BC

+1778-222-6960

sakura.nishiya@gmail.com

sakura.nishiya.com

in sakura-nishiya

sakura248

SUMMARY

Front-end web developer with a background in project management and a passion for solving problems and UI/UX . Experienced collaboration with the various people's concerns for 4 + years as a director in a Web design agency. I believe my background and passion for web development would contribute to your team.

SKILLS

React, Redux, JavaScript, Typescript, HTML, CSS, Firebase (Authentification, FIrestore cloud), Node.js, MongoDB, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, Git

PROJECTS

Favorite Quotes

Technical Specifications: React, Redux, Firebase Authentication, Firebase Firestore Database, The Movie Database (TMDB) API, Tailwind CSS

React app enable users to add/update their own favorite quotes from their favorite TV shows.

What to Wear

Technical Specifications: React, OpenWeatherMap API, CSS3

React app suggests what to wear depending on current temperature from OpenWeatherMap API

Blog crud app

Technical Specifications: React, Node.js, MongoDB Atlas, CSS3

Made this blog crud app to practice and learn $\ensuremath{\mathsf{MERN}}$ stack

EXPERIENCE

futurelabo, Tokyo, Japan | August 2020 - present

QA Tester / Customer Support / Admin

- Checked and tested issues in Gitlab.
- Gave instructions for UI improvements.
- Organized the operation of the customer support system.

Members *, Tokyo, Japan | April 2016 - August 2020

Web Director

- · Made proposals to improve the client's website UI/UX, managed the process and the schedule for modifications of over 100 pages.
- Voluntarily lead the weekly problem solving meeting for the operational mistakes and analyzed the proposed solutions which is more logical and feasible. As a result, nominated for annual best web director.
- Met 100% of deadlines, project goals was always dedicated. As a result, appointed as the web director and was assigned to client's challenging huge projects.
- Managed communication among 3 sectors, client, my company team and another vender to establish a schedule to ensure the client's website renewal project can be done by the due date.
- * Members is one of the biggest Tokyo-based digital agencies and well known for supporting major enterprises in Japan.

EDUCATION

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada, Vancouver, BC | May 2021 - present

Web Development Co-op Diploma

Tokyo Metropolitan University, Tokyo, Japan | April 2011 - March 2016

Bachelor of Sociology